[{"answer": "Sandy Hook school.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "This is 911, what's the location of the emergency?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "Because somebody's got a gun.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "OK, what makes you think that?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "I've heard a portion of the tapes, I don't think the timing is right for them to be released.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "First of all, let me get your reaction to the release of this 911 tapes, have you heard them yourself and what do you feel about the release today?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "It's been very trying, as a family that's been shaken to the core.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "As a member of the family, as a Lanza, have you been able to work out in your mind what on earth happened to turn Adam Lanza into this mass killer?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "No she did not, she said her boys were fine and she was looking into the education -- further education for Adam into Washington, you know, they were waiting to hear back.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "How did she seem to you then, did she mention any problems that she was having with her son?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "My heart goes out to each and every family that has lost a child.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "What are you as a member of the Lanza Family would you say to the families who lost their children that day and indeed the six adults who were also killed?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Like any of us it's been a real trial, my heart goes out to Peter, I can only imagine what he is enduring, it was his son.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Does he give any insight into he's been coping with what happened?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "I was at home, I had the TV on only for noise I really wasn't watching it and I caught glimpse that there had been a school shooting and I thought, \"Oh no not another one.\"", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "How did you hear the news and what was your reaction to when you discovered it was one of your own family who had perpetrated this terrible crime?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "For the most part people have been very kind to me.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "How do people treat the family generally?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "No I don't believe she deserves the criticism that she's gotten and why do I say that because, until you walked in her shoes as a parent with a special needs child you don't know what she endured, you don't know what she dealt with on a daily basis.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "You knew her, what do you think?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "You I believe had contact with Nancy Lanza on the very day of the atrocity via e-mail is that right?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "We were chatting about the boys and he going to Washington looking into some possible school.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "What did you say to it?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "She didn't relay how bad things were or if they were that bad.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "So she was really even then trying to deal with his problems you believe?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Well Nancy was a very gentle spirit, a very kind, very giving, very compassionate person, very generous, I always liked Nancy she was a good mom.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "What kind of a woman was she, Nancy Lanza?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "I guess my whole thoughts on the whole thing is let's back up to when he was in school and he was labeled to special needs.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Why do you think she was not able to spot that?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Oh, I want to say here on behalf of the Lanza family.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "What would you say on behalf of the Lanza family to people like Neil Heslin and the others as they still try and come to terms of what happened?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "I respect her for her coming forth and speaking.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "It was -- if felt good after I met with him spoke with him.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "What was that meeting like for you?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "I was aware of what was on most of the tapes or a lot of the tapes.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Do you have any intention of listening to it?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "I have to deal with it the same way as I dealt with it last year, you know, it's -- you can only try to imagine what it is, it's like to lose a child and unless you -- you've lost a child.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Has it gone for you that something that you could possibly enjoy?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "I don't think he failed.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "How do you feel as one of the parents about that?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "I mean, do you not want to see some legacy come out of this which actually goes someway to try to prevent it happening again?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "I was told by somebody down at Newtown that your wife has actually been invited to speak on the anniversary of Sandy Hook, is that true?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Yes, it is true and actually I'm praying for Kay, who I know I talked to her earlier today and she's studying for that.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "How do you feel as a family about that?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "I think the first thing that we need to say is that God is grieving too.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "What do you say to them from a religious faith point of view, to try and bring any kind of comfort, because it's clear to me when I speak to some of them now that time has not been a healer yet?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Well, I'm doing the same things that we talked about in that interview.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "How are you coping since I last spoke to you as a family?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "A month before he took his life.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "When did he finally get this gun?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "He told me that he -- he told me everything and he told me that he have found somebody finally on the internet who would sell it to him and it had to be super encrypted and it had to be, you know, this cool process and he begged me help him because he couldn't figure out the process and again there are so many -- so many moments of terrible choices with mental illness.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "And do you know how he got -- who he got it from?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "I think one of the reasons why it's being hard to tackle is because there are so many guns out there in the first place there are almost as many guns in America as our people.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "How do we get to grips with this?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "What does that tell you about the state of the debate about this everything else?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Most diet plans are pretty simplistic 'cause they only deal with food and fitness.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "What is the Daniel Plan, how are you going to get me healthier in 40 days?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "This one is actually on physical health and -- and actually the reason why is that I discovered that a lot people want to change, make changes in their life but they don't have the energy to make changes.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "... so that's impressive doesn't it?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "You know what's extraordinary Piers is that people change together in community.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Why should spirituality, the power of prayer, any of that stuff have any effect of my ability to be fit or lose weight?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "So there are a 140 studies now, that say as your weight goes up, the actual physical size, and function of your brain goes down.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "How are you going to convince people in their heads, never mind anything else, to come and do this because if this is the master plan you got to persuade them?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "That's true.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "When the brain smaller as you get fatter?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "The person with the good bottle of Jack Daniels.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "The person with the good brain or the person with the bad brain?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "So start reading the labels, so get on the internet--", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Does it matter?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "I mean it's very simple.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "So tell me what are you hoping, well these audience said, many of them have tried and failed with diets through their lives what is the key take away here from this book that can change things?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Yeah, plant food, nuts, seeds, beans, whole of grains--", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Plant food?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Me chicken, fish, all of those things are foods.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Can you eat as much wings as you like?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Sugar, flour, processed foods, factory foods,(inaudible), corn syrup, trans fats, MSG all these things that are -- the abundant things in our diet that are driving addiction--", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "What are the biggest no no's?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Well there are three things.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "What do you think has been the most effective thing for you in terms of loosing weight?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "You know, Christmas, there's three purposes of Christmas.", "docId": "131204pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "And Rick just a final question for you, obviously you said, the most difficult year of your life, how will you be spending Christmas this year as a family?", "qSentId": 444}]